This video will show you how to
modify an existing Open Case Study
for your own specific needs.
By the end of the demonstration,
you will know how to:
Find the case study GitHub repository
Clone or fork the case study
Open the case study source files in RStudio
Modify the source files
and finally, Compile the modified case study.
You can find the case study repository
using the Open Case Study Search tool on our website,
which is located on the bottom of the webpage,
or you can find it by clicking on the tab.
From here, you can locate the case study
you want to modify
and click on the repository link in
the GitHub repository column.
For this demonstration we will be using
the CO2 Emissions case study.
If your case study offers it, you can
select to edit either the static version repository
or the interactive version.
For this demonstration, we'll be using the static version.
You can also find a link to the
repository in the case study itself.
From here, you can clone and
fork the case study repository
using Git shell commands, or the new OCSdata package!
If you don't want the repository's version history,
you may also use the package to download
the case study as a zip file.
I will be using the zip file method
for this demonstration.
First, you'll need to install the OCSdata package
using the following command.
install.packages() and then in quotes "OCSdata"
[install.packages("OCSdata")]
Once that is finished, you now have access to
all of the functions available from OCSdata
So if you would like to clone or fork the
repository you may use the `clone_ocs()` function.
All you need is the repository name,
which we can get from GitHub.
You would like to set the outpath to specify where you
want it to download to.
We will just use our current working directory.
[getwd()]
And finally need to specify if you want to fork or clone it.
Set it to `FALSE` if you would like to clone
or `TRUE` if you would like to fork the repository.
[clone: fork_repo = FALSE; fork: fork_repo = TRUE]
However, we will not be using this function
for this demonstration.
Instead we'll be using the `zip_ocs()` function
which is structured similarly, we just need
the repository name
and to set where we want the case study
repository to be downloaded to.
We'll use our current working directory [getwd()]
for that as well.
So hit enter, it will automatically download
a zip file of the repository.
The function will automatically generate a random
name for the directory, as you can see at the top here.
But you are free to change this as you'd like.
Once the case study project opens automatically,
open the index.Rmd file
and scroll to the section that you want to edit.
For this demonstration, let's say that we want to
edit the data import section.
So you can just type directly into here:
"My new content... blah blah blah"
You can hit save, and then from here you'll move
to the knit dropdown menu.
You can choose which format you'd like to
compile your case study in, any of these are fine.
The Open Case Studies uses HTML files
so that we may host our case studies online.
But you can easily distribute your case study
to your students in any of these formats.
RStudio will automatically begin
compiling your case study
and once it is done it will automatically
render a preview of your case study.
In the preview you can scroll to the
section that you edited
and see your new content in the case study.
You can also see the compiled file in
your working directory: index.html.
This will say .pdf or .doc depending on
which one you picked.
That's all you have to do to modify a
case study! Thank you for watching.